Guide to the Cornell University Treasurer's records, 1908-1940
Cornell University Treasurer's records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Treasurer's records, 1908-1940
7-1-365
Cornell University. Treasurer.
69.2 cubic ft.
Financial materials and correspondence.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Financial records of various University departments, and correspondence with students, faculty, and staff; includes correspondence relating to student loans.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Financial records of various University departments, and correspondence with students, faculty, and staff; includes correspondence relating to student loans.
Includes collection 7-9-366.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University--Finance.; Cornell University--Administration.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Mann, Dean A.R. I, 1922-1923 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Mann, Dean A.R. II, 1922-1923 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Cornell Land and Power Co., 1925-1926 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Plan Commission, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Wisconsin Lands, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Lyon Hall, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Whaley-Eaton Service, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Whaley-Eaton Service, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Whaley-Eaton Service, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Cornell Observatory (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Studies for Cornell-Special Reference to the Location of the Buildings for the College of Agriculture, November 1910 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Needs of the NYS Colleges at Cornell, January 1910 (Box 1, Folder 12)